

# Gündüz Mammadli

# Frontend Developer

# **About Me**

As a Frontend developer, I have experience creating and maintaining user-facing web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React. I have a strong understanding of responsive design, cross-browser compatibility, and web accessibility standards. I have worked collaboratively with other developers, designers, and stakeholders to ensure that websites meet client and user requirements. I am committed to writing clean, efficient, and well-documented code, and staying up-to-date with the latest frontend development technologies and trends.

### My Contact

gunduz.mammadli@hotmail.com

+99470-718-96-28

Ilyas Aslanov str. Baku, Azerbaijan

https://portfoliopowerking.netlify.app

#### **Hard Skill**

- HTML5
- CSS3/SCSS/SASS
- TailwandCSS
- BootStrap
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Reactis
- Firebase

#### **Soft Skill**

- Communication
- Team-work
- Problem-solving
- nme management
- Adaptability
- Leadership
- Emotional
- intelligence
- SelfstudyHardworking
- Patience

### **Education Background**

- School N2 Zaporozhye, Ukraine Completed in 2010
- Baku State University Orientalism Completed in 2014

### **Language Skills**

- English-fluent
- Russian-native
- Azerbaijani-native
- Ukrainian-native
- Turkish-fluent
- Spanish-B1
- German-B1

# **Professional Experience**

#### OkMedia LLC

2023- Present

Junior Frontend Developer

#### **Courtyard Yard by Marriott Baku**

Guest Service Agent Jan 2021 – May 2022

#### Dinamo Hotel Baku Baku

Guest Relations Agent June 2019-Jan 2021

#### **Courses Attended**

Div Academy Baku Sep 2022 - Apr 2023